bluntcard.com 2015-06-16

# Bluntcard.com

**Bluntcard Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

Bluntcard.com itself collects no information from its visitors. However our use of Google ads on the site will attach a cookie. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We may release information (Google Analytics information or if you were to email Bluntcard directly, for example) when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.bluntcard.com/privacy.php).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on Feb, 2nd, 2012 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://bluntcard.com  
privacy@bluntcard.com
